Hello friends, in today's video I have again
brought a new update about PM Kisan Samman Nidhi, in which
friends I am going to tell you that if
friends your account is also activated but
friends the payment did not reach your account, then
friends what could be the reason for the
payment not going to your account, so
friends in today's video I will tell you till the end
that friends when you come here on the side,
friends you check friends
your status is to but the
payment did not go to your account, friends
what do you have to do, friends in today's video I am going to give
you complete information, so
friends let's start this video,
hello friends I am Prince,
welcome to Preet Left channel, if friends you are watching
my video for the first time, then
definitely subscribe to this channel and friends
I have pressed ignore so that friends
you can get the new video first,
friends let's start the channel, now here
friends when you come to this site, then friends when
you start your beneficiary chat, then
here friends your data is done, so
here friends you see
that your payment has been
received, but friends you  If you do
n't understand whether your payment has gone, then
friends, let me tell you that if
you have two accounts, friends, let me
tell you that if you have completed e-KYC,
then
friends, your payment will
not go to the account you had set up. Your payment will go to the account which is linked to your Aadhar card.
What do you have to do for this? Friends, in
your accounts which are closed,
friends, you have to check whether
your money has gone to those accounts.
Friends, you have to check
why your friends are being set here,
friends, your payment will go to that account. If you
read here, then your money will go to that account
which will show here. So
friends, keeping this in mind, you have to check your data
that your money has gone from the phone to the bank.
Now friends, I find that if
you have two Jatin accounts, friends,
your accounts are not working, friends, friends,
you are not using them, then
friends, get them closed. Because of this,
friends, let me tell you that you may suffer a loss. The
loss of this will be that
your money will go to those accounts.
Friends, you have closed your account
but your account is not active,
friends, that payment will go to your closed account, that is, friends,
your payment will go to the account which you are not using, so
friends, you have to
close that account which is
useless for you, friends, I will make it
clear to you, now friends, let me
tell you, friends, the payment of 13 has not come yet,
friends, what will you do if friends, your
account shows as active in your status, then
friends, you need to do an ABC,
then friends, your payment will come, for this,
friends, you can also go to the nearest CSC center and get
KYC done by fingerprint,
if friends, your Aadhar card
is linked to your mobile number, then friends, you can do it yourself from here also,
friends, this is very important,
if friends, your account has been deactivated, then friends,
for that, friends, I have already
made a video on what you have to do, friends,
above, friends, you will also find the video in the i button,
and friends, you will
also find the video below, so by watching
that video, friends, you
can find out your condition, if friends, your account has been
deactivated, then friends, that's all in today's
video, if you liked the video,
Please do like and share friends if
you have any doubts friends if
you have any problems you
can comment to us if you do
not want to ask for help on YouTube then
you can also ask for this help by messaging us personally on Instagram
friends
you will
see the Instagram logo on the screen above you can
go to it and ask for help
friends that's all for today's video
Jai Hind friends so
[Music]